<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Hybrid Modernization</title>
    <link href="https://www.hybridmodernization.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.hybridmodernization.com" />
    <updated>2022-11-03T15:57:10-04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Jon Kragh</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.hybridmodernization.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>The Hybrid Modernization Philosophy </title>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Kragh</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.hybridmodernization.com/hybrid-modernization.html"/>
        <id>https://www.hybridmodernization.com/hybrid-modernization.html</id>

        <updated>2022-11-03T15:57:10-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     "So the code that's the fastest to write, the code that's the easiest to maintain, and the code that never breaks, is the code you don't write. So that's our strategy, write a lot less code." Steve Jobs presenting NEXT computers to MIT in&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
    <figure class="blockquote">
      <blockquote>"So the code that's the fastest to write, the code that's the easiest to maintain, and the code that never breaks, is the code you don't write. So that's our strategy, write a lot less code."</blockquote>
      <figcaption>Steve Jobs presenting NEXT computers to MIT in 1992.</figcaption>
    </figure>

  <p>
    Hybrid Modernization is an approach to modernizing technology capabilities by bridging legacy systems with platform technologies including&nbsp;Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) and application layer low code and no code solutions.
  </p>

  <p>
    <a href="https://www.proactivelogic.com/">Proactive Logic Consulting Inc.</a> started using the term Hybrid Modernization to describe the approach using low code applications to produce high quality technical solutions faster than previous modernization approaches.&nbsp;
  </p>

  <p>
    The spirit of hybrid modernization is to do more with less by leveraging code and technologies managed at scale by other companies. As an industry, we started to see this shift in the cloud with a move from Infrastructure-as-a-Service (IaaS) to PaaS. Now our industry is shifting platform enablement to the application layer using low code toolsets across user interface, data integration, data storage, automation, machine learning, and business intellegence.<br>
  </p>

  <p>
    <b>Hybrid Modernization Principles</b>
  </p>

  <ol>
    <li><span style="color: var(--eb-text-primary-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: 1em; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Hybrid modernization solutions should drastically improve time-to-value by providing working software early and often.</span><br></li><li><span style="color: var(--eb-text-primary-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: 1em; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Hybrid modernization drives down the cost experimentation so that companies have more chances to discover a breakthrough with uncapped upside. In other words, more chances at bat to hit a ball that scores a thousand runs.<br></span></li><li>Hybrid modernization should reduce business risk by limiting the number of "no turning back" or very costly course changing decisions.</li><li>Hybrid modernization should produce usable applications on production data. In other words, early prototypes should create business value against production data.</li><li>Hybrid modernization apps should become more secure without explicit action. In other words, vendors should patch your applications to fix vulnerabilities.</li><li>Hybrid modernization solutions should favor no code or low code before writing custom code.<br></li><li>Hybrid modernization teams must shift from low cost individuals producing large swaths of hard to maintain code to high impact individuals that produce great solutions with less code and more great decisions.</li><li>Hybrid modernization teams must work directly with front line workers to solve real problems using a grass roots innovation approach.<br></li><li>Hybrid modernization teams have the ability to integrate complex backend systems using traditional high-code enterprise grade coding practices when appropriate.<br></li><li>Hybrid modernization solutions evolve to increase leverage by using new platform technologies to replace previous high-code solutions when new platform capabilities become available.<br></li>
  </ol>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
